LUIS MANUEL ZUÑIGA MORENO

System Engineer with an emphasis on software development

I am a PHP Backend developer with more than 7 years of experience in the field of development using Laravel and Symfony framework. I am very proactive in everything is assigned to me and I really like to learn every day. I feel comfortable working with Docker, Docker compose and using Jenkins for CI/CD; also, I use Git to control version in order to improve the project assigned to me and GitHub actions to build images for Docker Hub. I am highly discipline, and I am able to work in teams.



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Medellin, Colombia

August 2021 - Currently

 PHP middle - Laravel developer Cognox S.A.S.

Cartagena de Indias, Colombia October 2019 - May 2021 Coordinator Sifinca 2.0 project Araujo y Segovia S.A.

Monteria, Colombia January 2018 - October 2019 Software development Engineer Araujo y Segovia de Córdoba S.A.

Monteria, Córdoba October 2016 - July 2017 Software development Engineer UNICIA S.A.S.

Medellín, Colombia September 2015 -February 2016 Full-stack web developer EDUCATIC S.A.S

Medellín, Colombia November 2014 - April 2015 Software development Engineer EDUCATIC S.A.S

Monteria, Colombia

July 2011 - November 2011

System technician Instituto Tecnologico San Agustin

EDUCATION

Monteria, Córdoba 2009 - 2014 System Engineer with anemphasis on software development
 Fundación Universitaria San Martin

Monteria, Córdoba 2010 - 2012 • Computer and network technician Tecnologico San Agustin

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Email:

ing.luiszunigam@gmail.com

Address:

Calle 35 # 14B - 37 Barrio La Floresta - Montería -Córdoba

Cellphone:

(+57) 302 3741497

Date of born:

19-07-1992

Nationality:

Colombian

LinkedIn Link:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/devluism/

SKILLS

- PHP 7
- Laravel 8
- Symfony 5
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- CSS
- HTML5
- PostgreSQL
- Microsoft SQL Server
- MongoDB
- Redis
- SCRUM Methodology
- Docker
- Docker-compose
- Docker Swarm
- Jenkins
- Linux server
- API Rest JSON
- XML
- Teamwork

Languages

- Native Spanish
- English B1